{
	"data": [
    {
      "question": "___ we set off now? Tell me if you are ready!",
      "a": "Will",
      "b": "Shall",
      "c": "Ought",
      "d": "Would",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "\n- Will is used to show that someone is willing or ready to do something ",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Will you please go to Las Vegas with us? \"No ___.\"",
      "a": "shall not",
      "b": "wouldn't",
      "c": "shouldn't",
      "d": "won't",
      "answer": "2",
      "explain": "- Would not: used to say that someone refused to do something",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you like my new hat? \"I like it, but would you please _________ put it on the dining table?\"",
      "a": "don't",
      "b": "not",
      "c": "doesn't",
      "d": "not to",
      "answer": "4",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Edward's score on the final exam is the highest in the class ___.",
      "a": "He should have studied overnight",
      "b": "He should study overnight",
      "c": "He must study overnight",
      "d": "He must have studied overnight",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Must: \t used to say you think something is very likely to be true or very likely to have happened",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "This ___ be a man's handkerchief. It must be a woman's.",
      "a": "can not",
      "b": "may not",
      "c": "must not",
      "d": "shall not",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "\n- Shall: used to emphasize that something will definitely happen, or that you are determined that something should happen",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Kent must be from the south, ___ ?",
      "a": "needn't he",
      "b": "mustn't he",
      "c": "may not he",
      "d": "isn't he",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Need: used in negative sentences when saying that something is not necessary or not always true",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Nobody _________ that by his ear.",
      "a": "dare says",
      "b": "dares say",
      "c": "dare say",
      "d": "dare saying",
      "answer": "3",
      "explain": "- Dare has both a modal use (he dare not do it), and a non-modal use (he doesn't dare to do it)",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "That guy was taken away by the police. He ___ for a thief, a robber or a murderer.",
      "a": "must be mistaken",
      "b": "must mistake",
      "c": "must have mistaken",
      "d": "must have been mistaken",
      "answer": "4",
      "explain": "- Must: \t used to say you think something is very likely to be true or very likely to have happened",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Terry used to go hiking on weekends, ___?",
      "a": "didn't he",
      "b": "used he",
      "c": "did he",
      "d": "usedn't he to",
      "answer": "1",
      "explain": "- Use an auxiliary verb when you want to avoid repeating some part of your sentence \n\n+ Used-> did",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    },
    {
      "question": "It is surprising to Teddy's family and all his friends that he ___ marry such an ugly woman.",
      "a": "should",
      "b": "would",
      "c": "shall",
      "d": "will",
      "answer": "2",
      "category": "1",
      "subcategorylv1": "35",
      "subcategorylv2": "10",
      "type": "1"
    }
  ]
}